http://www.tamge.com/privacy-policy/

Toggle navigation
Menu
Login / Register
All Categories
Certification Testers (8)Cleaning Kits and Other (1)Cleavers (7)Fiber Holders (2)Fiber Rings / Launch-Receive Cables (1)Fusion Splicers (27)Inspection Microscope/Video (1)Optical Fiber Identifiers (1)Optical Loss Test Kits (1)OTDR (35)Power Meter & Light Sources (2)Splicing Equipment (38)Test Equipment (41)
0
Cart
$0.00
Toggle navigation
Home
Shop
Shop
Checkout
Home » Privacy Policy
Tamge  (Test and Measurement Global Exchange) respects the privacy of its customers and visitors. If you have any questions about the operation of our website, please write to sales@tamge.com.
Our website collects names, email addresses, and other personal information from customers and visitors only when submitted via one of our online forms, such as our Quick Quote form, Quick Bid form, or our standard contact form. This data is used solely by Tamge and is not shared, traded, or sold to third parties—unless customers or registrants opt to receive information from like-minded organizations, in which case we share only names, email addresses, and postal addresses.
Our web-server also records IP addresses from all visitors to our site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, to analyze trends, to track user movement, and to gather broad demographic information—all for the purpose of continually improving our website and delivering personalized, custom content. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information, and their collection is standard procedure in most web-server environments.
Our website contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website, for which Tamge is not responsible.
By using tamge.com, you signify your agreement to our privacy policy as stated above. Note that this policy may be revised periodically without notice. Please re-read this policy prior to submitting any personal information if you have concerns about how your information is being collected and used.
Search for:
